sneakerobsession.com 2012-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Sneaker Obsession

Privacy Policy for SneakerObsession.com

SneakerObsession.com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. “Period.”

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters. You may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, and other interactive areas of our site. Like most Web sites, SneakerObsession.com also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences.

Like many other Web sites, SneakerObsession.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP) addresses, browser history, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on SneakerObsession.com to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by SneakerObsession.com and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by SneakerObsession.com may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

SneakerObsession.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a SneakerObsession.com page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through www.SneakerObsession.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. SneakerObsession.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. SneakerObsession.com does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on SneakerObsession.com.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to SneakerObsession.com and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Linkshare  
Google Affiliate Network

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on SneakerObsession.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

SneakerObsession.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. SneakerObsession.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

SneakerObsession.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe SneakerObsession.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed below.

We can be reached by contacting:  
Email: sneakerobsession@gmail.com

SneakerObsession.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by New York law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: New York. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following location: New York, under the rules of the American Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.

SneakerObsession.com is controlled, operated and administered entirely within New York. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

_Last updated: April 6, 2012_
